# **BRAYDON HUNT**

Accomplished delivery driver with seven years' experience meeting tight delivery deadlines and offering outstanding customer service. Able to manage own time efficiently and work effectively in a fast-paced role. Can communicate clearly with colleagues and customers, with a foe us on meeting and exceeding client expectations to increase brand loyalty.

123 My Street, San Francisco, CA 56789 b. h u nt@exa mple.com (123)-456-7890

### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### PACKAGE DELIVERY DRIVER

UPS, San Francisco, CA January 2014 - Present

- Safely load, lower, and carry large packages weighing up to 70 pounds
- ◆ Drive manual transmission delivery vehicles safely according to local traffic laws in all weather conditions to protect employer's property and the public
- Manage time carefully to provide a punctual and friendly service to customers in line with the company's brand image
- ◆ Su ppo rt less ex perien ced tea m mem bers to deve lop c u stom e r service skills and local route knowledge

## **FOOD DELIVERY DRIVER**

Safeway, San Francisco, CA November 2013 - January 2014

- Maintained cleanliness of delivery vehicle and performed vehicle safety checks before starting a shift
- Effectively utilized Safeway's GPS, following the most efficient routes to make timely deliveries in heavy traffic
- Loaded and organized goods carefully to prevent damage and ensure all deliveries arrived in perfect condition
- Reported delays and traffic incidents to the management team

#### **EDUCATION**

High School Diploma

Balboa High School, San Francisco, CA September 2009 - July 2013

# **KEY SKILLS**

- Handle long shifts on multi-drop routes
- Veh ic le mainten a rice
- Warm a nd friend I y c ustomer service
- Timekeeping and meeting challenging deadlines
- Work i ng co 11 a bora t i ve ly wit h a team
- Strong knowledge of local routes and traffic restrictions

# **CERTIFICATIONS**

- ♦ Valid Driver's License
- ♦ CDL Class B, expires August 2021